Luis Manuel Zuñiga Moreno

Montería, Córdoba, Colombia



ing.luiszunigam@gmail.com



3104052643



linkedin.com/in/devluism



https://devluismanuel.github.io

Summary

I am a PHP Backend Developer with more than 7 years of experience using Laravel and Symfony framework, I like working with Docker, Docker-compose and I use Jenkins for CI/CD; In addition, I use Git as version control in order to improve the project that is assigned to me and GitHub Actions to perform CI/CD as well.

Lover of continuous learning, I am very disciplined, capable of working in a team and in the future, I would like to be a Technical Leader as well as continue working remotely.

My native language is Spanish, but I really like the English language, my current level is B1, but with the idea of continuing to improve it more and more.

Experience



Desarrollador PHP Backend

Cognox

Aug 2021 - Present (9 months +)

- Development of PHP Backend using Laravel 8 Framework, GraphQL and Docker for the company's private project using Scrum and Jenkins methodology for CI.

Tech stack: PHP | Laravel | Jenkins | GraphQL | Docker | Scrum



CEO, Backend Developer Senior

Freelance Web Development

Apr 2016 - Present (6 years 1 month +)

- Internal network construction, and internal site construction based on a dynamic web using Laravel 6 as Backend and Vue.js as Frontend, this in order to recreate the different animals in wildlife, a project carried out for the Regional Autonomous Corporation of the valleys of Sinú and San Jorge (CVS)
- CRM application maintenance using PHP 6 for real estate Medellin Properties.
- Development of a dynamic web page using Backend Laravel 5.5 and Blade for Frontend, this development was carried out for the Inmobiliaria Medellín Properties in the city of Medellín, Antioquia, (https://medellinproperties.com).
- Development of PQR'S software for shopping centers, using Laravel 6, as Front and Backend.
- Development of order taking software for restaurants, developed in Laravel 6 as Backend and Frontend, as well as making billing printing module using API as internal connections.
- Development of software for sales management, carried out in Laravel 8 and Vue. is 3, this project was carried out for the company SURTIMED SUMINISTROS S.A.S.

Tech stack: PHP | Laravel | Jenkins | GraphQL | Docker | Scrum | Javascript | VueJs | HTML | CSS



Ingeniero de desarrollo de software

Gml Software Oficial

Jun 2021 - Aug 2021 (3 months)

Tech stack: PHP | Laravel | Javascript | VueJs | HTML | CSS



Coordinador Proyecto Sifinca 2.0

ARAUJO Y SEGOVIA

Oct 2019 - May 2021 (1 year 8 months)

- Assign and monitor the tasks of each of the programmers in the area.
- Establish the guidelines regarding the tools, methodology and times of the Development area.
- Provide feedback to senior management on the progress of the tasks in execution in the Development area.
- Manage the necessary resources for the optimal functioning of the Development area.
- Lead research for the adoption of new technologies to apply to developed products.
- Support the team in the execution of their tasks.
- Responsible for the proper functioning of the company's infrastructure, such as cloud instances using GCP, as well as local virtual servers using Proxmox and VirtualBox.
- Develop modules that were requested in the siFinca2.0 project, using Symfony Framework and Javascript.
- Development of the infrastructure in the development area using Docker, Docker-compose and using the Docker-Swarm orchestrator for local deployments.

Tech stack: PHP |Symphony | Docker | Scrum | Docker-compose | Docker-swarm | IT



Ingeniero de desarrollo de software

ARAUJO Y SEGOVIA

Jan 2018 - Oct 2019 (1 year 10 months)

- Maintenance of the siFinca2.0 project using the Symfony 2.8 Framework and Javascript.
- Development of new modules to the siFinca2.0 project, such as billing, commands, among others.

Tech stack: PHP | Symphony | JavaScript | Html | Css | PostgreSQL



Ingeniero de Desarrollo de Software

UNICIA S.A.S.

Oct 2016 - Jul 2017 (10 months)

- Creation of templates and reports in SQL Server.
- Maintenance to CLINTOS Software.

Tech stack: SqlServer



Full-Stack Web Developer

Educatic S.A.S

Sep 2015 - Feb 2016 (6 months)

- EDUCATIC software maintenance, using Hibernate, Struts as Backend in JAVA, as well as HTML and CSS as Frontend.

Tech stack: Java | HTML | CSS

Ingeniero de soporte de software

Educatic S.A.S

Nov 2014 - Apr 2015 (6 months)

- EDUCATIC software maintenance, using Hibernate, Struts as Backend in JAVA, as well as HTML and CSS as Frontend.

Tech stack: Java | HTML | CSS

Tecnico en Sistemas

Instituto Tecnologico San Agustin Jun 2011 - Nov 2011 (6 months)

Education

Fundación Universitaria San Martín

Ingeniero de Sistemas, Desarrollo de software 2009 - 2014

Tecnológico San Agustín

Técnico laboral en Informática y Redes, Desarrollo de Software 2010 - 2012

[ly] Talently

Mar 2022 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

iniciando con Containers en Docker - Udemy UC-UO00T866

O Aprende Docker desde Cero a Swarm y Kubernetes - Udemy

UC-195ec229-58dc-4ff3-8f2b-258659cbe744

DevOps con Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, git, GitFlow Cl y CD - Udemy UC-6380f0c9-d123-4b80-b8cd-f4a98054cd23

Skills

JavaScript • PHP • Web Applications • Web Services • MySQL • Web Development • Jenkins • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)